Curtis Arey, Jr.

103 S Home Ave Topton PA 19562 csareyj@gmail.com (484)554-7204

Objective

With more than 8 years of customer service experience, I'm looking to utilize and expand my knowledge and skills within a growing company and take full advantage of my potential.

Skills - Proficient with Microsoft Office (Excel, Word, PowerPoint, etc.). Extensive knowledge and understanding of medical terminology, billing and claims. Ability to handle heavy call volumes and inbound/outbound telephone usage. Typing 90+ wpm while multitasking with up to 15 computer programs.

Education

William Allen High School – Graduated June 2010 University of Pennsylvania Full Stack Coding Bootcamp – August 2022

Experience

June 2018-- Current

SG Homecare

Biller

Receiving inbound calls answering any and all questions they may have, educating patients on their current balance and billing procedures/protocol for durable medical equipment (DME). Understanding Medicare's pricing and allowable rates as well as contracted billing and allowable rates with payers we contract with. Understanding how durable medical equipment works, how often patients need/get supplies for them. Verifying patient eligibility and DME benefits for over 15 contracted medical groups and health plans by phone via outbound calls. Reviewing authorizations, as well as working directly with insurance claims involving submissions (with primary EOB if applicable) and corrections. Working in a fast pace, growing environment in close coordination with my colleagues to assist patient's with satisfaction in first call resolution.

August 2017 -- June 2018

Advanced Disposal

Customer Service Representative

Assist customers and commercial businesses with starting new trash/recycling services, cancelling existing trash/recycling services, helping and educating customers on their billing, and also resolving any service issues they may have. Ability to multitask, navigating between 8 or more computer systems, from data entry to outbound correspondence. Empathize greatly with customers and listen to really understand the customer's situation in order to meet the customer's needs. Excel in accurately finding our member's location, this way the driver finds them without a problem and service's the member in a timely manner. Educate members on t other services we provide and offer a variety of opportunities or discounts they may have. Ability to adhere to schedule and call volume needs. Work in a fast pace growing environment while working closely with my colleagues to successfully ensure a positive and promising customer relationship.

March 2015 - Sept 2017

Aetna Life Insurance Inc.

Customer Service Representative

Assist Members with eligibility, claims and benefit questions all over the country. Adjusting/Correcting Coordination of Benefits and working closely with the claims processing team to ensure members never have any issues. Navigate between 15 or more computer systems, from data entry to outbound correspondence. Empathize greatly with members and work in conjunction with my colleagues to meet consumer demands. Keeping the commitment to the member by following up with them or taking them out of the middle, making things easier for them. Educate members on things they may not know about their plans and offer a variety of opportunities or alternatives they may have to. Proficient with claims processing and billing. Ability to multitask and complete required responsibilities accurately on time. Ability to adhere to schedule and call volume needs. Work in a fast pace growing environment while working closely with my colleagues to successfully ensure excellent consumer satisfaction.

September 2014 -- March 2015

Community Health Systems (CHS)

Customer Service Representative

Assist patients with billing for over 16 different hospitals. Navigate between 15 or more computer systems. Use strong interpersonal skills to work closely with my peers as a high functioning team. Familiar with claim & billing processing. Ability to multi-task and complete required responsibilities accurately and on time. Print/Mail out patient Itemized bills or payment receipts. Verifying insurance eligibility for patients via Passport/Navanet. Build trust and long lasting positive relationships with customers while focusing on first call resolution. Always provide customers options and never leave them with a close ended negative answer. Work in a fast pace high demand environment while successfully serving customers and leading my teammates to success.